<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.knime.features.gateway.rest.local"
      label="KNIME Remote Gateway via REST (experimental, don&apos;t install)"
      version="4.8.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="KNIME AG, Zurich, Switzerland">

   <description>
      This features contains the client-side libraries for connecting
to a KNIME server via the REST gateway API. It mainly enables
remote
access to jobs on the server, e.g. to be viewed via the KNIME
explorer.
This feature and the contained plug-ins are the intellectual
property of KNIME AG, Zurich, Switzerland. 
This plug-in is not part of the Open Source KNIME Platform. 
It is not released under GPL, like most parts of KNIME. It 
is available at no charge and it can be used without 
restrictions. It is provided &quot;as is&quot;, without any warranty. 
You may NOT freely copy it, nor modify or distribute it. 
For details, please refer to the license agreement.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright by KNIME AG, Zurich, Switzerland
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      Terms for License of the KNIME Job View for KNIME Analytics Platform (AP)
via REST
1. Application
1.1 These terms regulate the conclusion, content and performance
of contracts with respect to the use of the software KNIME Job
View for AP, which is available for download from the website
http://www.knime.com (&quot;Website&quot;) (&quot;KNIME Job View&quot;).
1.2 These terms shall be deemed accepted as soon as the user
(&quot;Licensee&quot;) downloads the KNIME Job View for AP.
2. Ownership
The KNIME Job View for AP is a copyrighted work owned by KNIME, 
Zurich, Switzerland (&quot;KNIME&quot;), or a third party.
3. License
3.1 The Licensee is granted a non-exclusive and worldwide right
to use the KNIME Job View for AP.
3.2 The Licensee may make copies of the KNIME Job View for
installation and backup purposes only.
4. Restrictions
4.1 Licensee shall not and agrees not to transfer, rent, sublicense,
copy, alter, modify, create derivative works of, reverse engineer,
disassemble (except as permitted by law) or distribute the KNIME
Job View for AP or any part thereof. 
4.2 KNIME reserves any rights not expressly granted to the
Licensee and retains all rights, title to and interest in the
KNIME Job View for AP.
5. WARRANTY AND LIABILITY
5.1 THE KNIME Job View for AP IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT
WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED
BY LAW, ALL WARRANTY IS EXCLUDED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
TO, WARRANTIES FOR UNINTERRUPTED AND ERROR-FREE OPERATION, FOR
OPERATION IN COMBINATION WITH OTHER HARDWARE, SOFTWARE, SYSTEMS
OR DATA, FOR MERCHANTABILITY, FOR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
AND FOR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS.
5.2 TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ALL LIABILITY OF KNIME.COM
IS HEREBY WAIVED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LIABILITY FOR
FINANCIAL DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE AND PERSONAL INJURY IN CONNECTION
WITH THE USE OF THE KNIME Job View for AP, LOSS OF DATA,
DAMAGE OF DATA, DAMAGE TO COMPUTER SYSTEMS, FUNCTIONAL DISRUPTION
OF COMPUTER SYSTEMS, DAMAGE OR LOSS OF PROFITS DUE TO THE WRONGFUL
OPERATION OR NON-OPERATION OF THE KNIME Example Server View.
6. Duration of contract
6.1 This license contract is concluded for an indefinite period.
6.2 However, KNIME may terminate this contract at any time
without financial consequences in case the Licensee is in breach
of the contract. In the events of such termination, the Licensee
shall cease to use the KNIME Job View for AP and destroy
all copies in his/her possession immediately.
7. Data Protection
KNIME complies with the applicable Swiss data protection
laws. The Licensee consents to KNIME using the Licensee&apos;s
personal data for its own marketing purposes.
8. General
8.1 All reports, requests and other communication shall be deemed
effective upon dispatch to the last address communicated to the
other party of this contract.
8.2 If any provision of this contract shall be judged to be invalid,
that provision shall be replaced by an economically equivalent
provision and the remaining provisions of this contract will
remain in full force and effect.
9. Applicable Law and Place of Jurisdiction
9.1 This contract shall be governed by Swiss law, excluding its
conflicts of laws principles and the Vienna Convention on the
Sale of Goods and Services.
9.2 Exclusive place of jurisdiction shall be the city of Zurich/Switzerland.
KNIME is, however, entitled to take legal action before any
competent court at the domicile of the Licensee.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="com.knime.gateway.local"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.knime.gateway"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.knime.gateway.json"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.knime.gateway.rest.local"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.knime.enterprise.gateway.rest.api"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
